Register of the Raymond Albert Wheeler papers, 1898-1977
Hoover Institution Archives
- Declassified U.S. Government Records, 1951-1970 (Box 52)
  - 2015 May release of records, 1951-1969 (Box-folder 52: 1-5)
    Correspondence, telegrams (with an accompanying index), memoranda, reports, and meeting minutes that largely pertain to the activities of the United Nations and the International Bank for Reconstruction and Development (World Bank). They provide details of Wheeler's professional involvement with various projects internationally, including the Suez Canal and the Mekong River Basin, among others.
  - 2016 February release of records, 1970 (Box-folder 52: 6)
    Letter from Brigadier General Edwin F. Black to General Wheeler relating to a proposal for a "major post-war program of regional development in Southeast Asia " and enclosing a memorandum on the subject of creating a Southeast Asia Regional Development Engineering Agency.